<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<anime id="4" restricted="false">
<type>TV Series</type>
<episodecount>13</episodecount>
<startdate>2000-04-14</startdate>
<enddate>2000-07-14</enddate>
<titles>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="main">Seikai no Senki</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="synonym">Battle Flag of the Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="zh-Hans" type="synonym">星界的战旗</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BotS1</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BotS</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="short">BFotS</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnS</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat" type="short">SnS1</title>
<title xml:lang="ja" type="official">星界の戦旗</title>
<title xml:lang="en" type="official">Banner of the Stars</title>
<title xml:lang="ko" type="official">성계의 전기</title>
</titles>
<relatedanime>
<anime id="5" type="Sequel">Seikai no Senki II</anime>
<anime id="1" type="Prequel">Seikai no Monshou</anime>
<anime id="884" type="Summary">Seikai no Senki Tokubetsu Hen</anime>
</relatedanime>
<similaranime>
<anime id="584" approval="65" total="74">Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu</anime>
</similaranime>
<recommendations total="8">
<recommendation type="For Fans" uid="37313">I agree with  theslo1 that Banner of the star is the weakest that its predecessor. The space battle aren`t that bad, but they lacking the dramatic tension in the despiction of war (We`re very far from LOGH in that area). With most of time time spend of the conflict, the character developpement take quite a backseat, even thou there some nice improvement near the end. Even so, it`s still and an enjoyable ride recommended for those who like Crest of the star...</recommendation>
<recommendation type="Recommended" uid="181366">Space opera at its best. Well executed plot, although not very surprising. Character development is slower considering the one from Crest of the Stars, but also very good. And then there are the space battles, strategy, plausible space travel technology... Top notch. All this is actually very similar to space battles from the Honorverse books, and that`s a good thing.

Note: EN voice cast is horrible, totally changes feeling of many conversations. Go for JAP one, it`s exceptionally good.</recommendation>
</recommendations>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/seikai/</url>
<creators>
<name id="4516" type="Character Design">Watabe Keisuke</name>
<name id="4303" type="Music">Hattori Katsuhisa</name>
<name id="4234" type="Direction">Nagaoka Yasuchika</name>
<name id="4495" type="Original Work">Morioka Hiroyuki</name>
<name id="4516" type="Chief Animation Direction">Watabe Keisuke</name>
<name id="3780" type="Chief Animation Direction">Shino Masanori</name>
</creators>
<description>* Based on the sci-fi novel series by http://anidb.net/cr4495 [Morioka Hiroyuki].
Three years after their adventure, http://anidb.net/ch28 [Lafiel] becomes captain on the brand new assault ship Basroil and http://anidb.net/ch4081 [Jinto] finishes his training to become a supply officer and joins Lafiel`s crew. They set out to join a large fleet with the mission to defend the strategically important Aptic Gate from a force 15 times larger than their own. And to make matters worse, their new fleet commander is from the http://anidb.net/ch4095 [Bebaus] family, a family notorious for their "Spectacular Insanity".
Source: ANN</description>
<ratings>
<permanent count="3334">8.00</permanent>
<temporary count="3358">8.23</temporary>
<review count="6">8.49</review>
</ratings>
<picture>18365.jpg</picture>
<categories>
<category id="174" parentid="8" hentai="false" weight="500">
<name>Space Travel</name>
<description>Space Travel usually refers going to space or travelling there with or without a spacecraft. There are different forms of space travel like Interplanetary travel, Interstellar travel or Intergalactic travel. Since it isn`t possible to travel faster than light, most anime series involve some sort "sub-space travel mechanism" as a way to travel faster than light.</description>
</category>
<category id="274" parentid="268" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Novel</name>
<description>Note that novel means book with words in paper, so no comics and no "visual novels", which should go under manga and dating-sim - visual Novel/erotic game respectively.

Note that it can be applied to novels as we know them but also the typical light novels for teens and young adults, which are common in Japan and aside from being short include a number of illustrations.</description>
</category>
<category id="12" parentid="6" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Future</name>
<description>Anime that fall under the future category are the ones that have a society that could have originated from ours. In most cases it should go hand to hand with sci-fi since we expect the future to consist of advanced technology, however, in the case where it`s explicitly stated in the story that the anime takes place "x years into the future", the state of technology doesn`t matter as long as it`s long into the future. The anime can be set in an alternative universe not tied with our own, as long as it has a futuristic feel to it.&#13;
&#13;
This category sports quite a lot of anime, mostly stemming from SciFi, but not necessarily only from there.</description>
</category>
<category id="129" parentid="19" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Shipboard</name>
<description>Beam me up, Scotty! Space stations (think Death Star) also count. Basically, this category is to tell if the setting takes place onboard a spaceship in space. This category is not applicable if the spaceship lies on a planet and never actually gets into space.</description>
</category>
<category id="19" parentid="7" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Space</name>
<description>The final frontier.</description>
</category>
<category id="198" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Romance</name>
<description>Romance describes a story that deals with love between two or more characters typically also having an optimistic ending. Romance is also a difficulty encountered when creating a harem.</description>
</category>
<category id="4" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Action</name>
<description>Action anime usually involve a fairly straightforward story of good guys versus bad guys, where most disputes are resolved by using physical force. It often contains a lot of shooting, explosions and fighting. </description>
</category>
<category id="8" parentid="313" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Sci-Fi</name>
<description>Science fiction stories usually focus on how situations could be different in the future when we are more technologically advanced; due to either our own achievements or having met with other civilizations whom we have learned from. </description>
</category>
<category id="171" parentid="317" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Military</name>
<description>The anime concerns an organised armed force, and its members. Said body should have both the equipment and hierarchy found in military groups, and should ideally be actively utilising their power against an opponent. Characters are either employed as professional soldiers or enlisted on a volunteer basis, for ideological reasons.</description>
</category>
<category id="233" parentid="216" hentai="false" weight="600">
<name>Plot Continuity</name>
<description>Consistency of the characteristics of persons, plot, objects, places and events seen by the viewer.&#13;
&#13;
A single linear focused plot is highly continuous.&#13;
&#13;
A truly random plot is highly discontinuous.</description>
</category>
<category id="259" parentid="171" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Airforce</name>
<description>Anime with this category, like anime with Military as category concerns an organised armed force, but with the difference that they should primarily conduct aerial warfare.&#13;
&#13;
Note: Just because the anime contains a bunch of planes or similar, unless the anime is actually about a fighting airforce, you might not want to add this genre. </description>
</category>
<category id="328" parentid="8" hentai="false" weight="100">
<name>Human Enhancement</name>
<description>The enhancement of humans can take various forms: It can be something comparatively non-intrusive as a power-up drug, a form of machine implantation or cyberization ("SAC Solid State Society"), or outright - possibly atrocious - genetic manipulation ("Ao no 6-gou"). Plot-wise enhanced protagonists in anime usually have to pay a price for their enhancements, be it physical or mental. </description>
</category>
<category id="329" parentid="328" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Genetic Modification</name>
<description>Story-wise Genetic Modification is usually centred on humans, probably the most subtle and creepy way of messing with mankind. Playing with the fear of the unknown, genetically altered humans are technically a new species, that may not only surpass but actually replace unaltered humans. The level of modification will vary from subtle changes in "look" (e.g. super-human beauty), to mental enhancements (PSI powers), to more or less atrocious adaptations to extreme environments (breath under water, radiation resistance). Note that changes in Aliens would be difficult to pinpoint, after all they are alien.</description>
</category>
<category id="221" parentid="15" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>Elf</name>
<description>Elf, in common description, near-divine beings, with pointed ears and immortal life-spans. They are sage beings that occupy the realms and gates between humanity and the gods.</description>
</category>
<category id="88" parentid="83" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Nudity</name>
<description>Nudity is the state of wearing no clothing and exposing the bare skin or intimate parts.

Especially gratuitous fanservice shows tend to show their characters frequently without any clothes, though often hiding genitals through the means of additions like steam.</description>
</category>
<category id="467" parentid="461" hentai="false" weight="400">
<name>War</name>
<description>An armed conflict is the main theme or plays a large role in this anime.</description>
</category>
<category id="505" parentid="198" hentai="false" weight="300">
<name>Slow When It Comes to Love</name>
<description>The main protagonists in this anime have a very hard time trying to express their feelings to each other. They simply will not finally confess their love.&#13;
&#13;
In some cases this romance element is based on unrequited love, or an absurd amount of shyness.</description>
</category>
</categories>
<resources>
<resource type="1">
<externalentity>
<identifier>447</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="2">
<externalentity>
<identifier>396</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="3">
<externalentity>
<identifier>368</identifier>
<identifier>fxbchz</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="4">
<externalentity>
<url>http://www.sunrise-inc.co.jp/seikai/</url>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="6">
<externalentity>
<identifier>Banner_of_the_Stars</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="7">
<externalentity>
<identifier>星界の戦旗</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="8">
<externalentity>
<identifier>1395</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="9">
<externalentity>
<identifier>159941</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
<resource type="14">
<externalentity>
<identifier>11600</identifier>
</externalentity>
</resource>
</resources>
<tags>
<tag id="199" approval="1" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2009-05-22">
<name>twins</name>
<count>131</count>
<description>Twin siblings featured in the cast.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="357" approval="8" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2013-07-07">
<name>cat</name>
<count>200</count>
<description>The cat is a small, usually furry, domesticated, and carnivorous mammal that is valued by humans for companionship and its ability to hunt vermin and household pests. Cats have been associated with humans for at least 9,500 years and are the most popular pet in the world. They have bodies adapted to killing small prey and are skilled predators, hunting over 1,000 species for food. Despite being solitary hunters, they`re a social species with many means of communication.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="175" approval="24" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2013-02-28">
<name>space elves</name>
<count>13</count>
<description>Extraterrestrial creatures with elven characteristics (pointed ears, superhuman intelligence, wisdom, lifespan or similar).</description>
</tag>
<tag id="136" approval="24" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2010-08-12">
<name>space opera</name>
<count>94</count>
<description>Space opera is a sub-genre of fiction that emphasizes romantic adventures in space. Space opera generally involves large-scale conflicts between opponents with powerful abilities and technology. The genre will often be melodramatic, sometimes playing music that can be nothing short of awesome. Warfare and a battle of wits are usually less emphasized, preferring romance (with exceptions, e.g. Ginga Eiyuu Densetsu). Some space operas tend to be formulaic and sometimes even prosaic, often employing very simple devices and somewhat obvious strategies. An example of this would be the infamous laws of physics in the Macross universe, in which the main male lead will hardly ever get hit in battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="393" approval="22" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2008-06-02">
<name>space battles</name>
<count>89</count>
<description>There are space battles in this anime. Usually between Earth forces and some alien invader, but ship to ship skirmishes in deep space are just as common.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1351" approval="15" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2012-02-15">
<name>sociocultural evolution</name>
<count>96</count>
<description>Describes how cultures and societies develop over time, based on both cultural evolution and social evolution.
A post-apocalyptic or a Utopian setting would show very interesting changes in human behaviour, mental state, or simply daily life.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1642" approval="16" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2010-07-31">
<name>fictional language</name>
<count>17</count>
<description>Fictional languages are intended to be the languages of a fictional world and are often designed with the intent of giving more depth and an appearance of plausibility to the fictional worlds with which they are associated, and to have their characters communicate in a fashion which is both alien and dislocated.
Some of these languages, e.g. in worlds of fantasy fiction, alternative universes, Earth`s future, or alternate history, are presented as distorted versions or dialects of modern English or other natural language, while others are independently designed conlangs.
A fictional language often has the least amount of grammar and vocabulary possible, and rarely extends beyond the absolutely necessary. At the same time, some others have developed languages in detail for their own sake, such as J. R. R. Tolkien`s Quenya and Sindarin and Star Trek`s Klingon language which exist as functioning, usable languages. Here "fictional" can be a misnomer.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2250" approval="10" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2014-02-09">
<name>strategic battle plans</name>
<count>25</count>
<description>There are scenes in which one or more characters devise and discuss strategies for a battle.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="2975" approval="7" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2009-06-24">
<name>flashback</name>
<count>390</count>
<description>The characters remember things from their past triggering a flashback. The anime either repeats scenes from previous episodes (danger of too many "fillers"), or actually shows new footage from very old memories.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="1995" approval="2" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2008-08-30">
<name>realistic space battles</name>
<count>4</count>
</tag>
<tag id="561" approval="20" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2010-11-29">
<name>strong female lead</name>
<count>412</count>
<description>The lead female character has a strong personality and plays a part that is not the typical damsel-in-distress role. 
This is the exact opposite of the “damsel in distress” tag.</description>
</tag>
<tag id="3725" approval="7" spoiler="false" localspoiler="false" globalspoiler="false" update="2011-04-18">
<name>dialogue driven</name>
<count>91</count>
<description>The plot of the anime is advanced by hopefully interesting and intriguing dialogues. Action is clearly of very much lower priority.</description>
</tag>
</tags>
<characters>
<character id="28" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="684">9.41</rating>
<name>Abriel Nei Debrusc Borl Paryun Lafiel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Ablïarsec néïc Dubreuscr Bœrh Parhynr Lamhirh (a.k.a., Viscountess Paryunu Abriel Nei Dobrusk Lafiel) is the main female protagonist in the anime Crest of the Stars, Banner of the Stars, and Banner of the Stars II, as well as all the novels written by Morioka Hiroyuki on which the shows were based. She is a strong-willed Abh princess (granddaughter of the Abh empress) who has a steely exterior, but ends up befriending Ghintec Linn (Jinto Lynn in the Martinh tongue). Like all Abh, she has bluish hued hair, and has a natural lifespan of over 200 years. Lamhirh also has lapis lazuli colored eyes. As an Ablïarsec, she has pointed ears, yet hers are markedly less so than other Ablïarsec. This is because half her genes (those not from her father) are from someone outside the Abriel clan and her father chose not to make any unnecessary alterations in her genes. She is deemed "child of love" (an Abh child with the genes of the parent, and the one the parent loves). Her full name can be roughly translated to Lamhirh (néïc Dubleuscr) Ablïarsec, Viscountess of Parhyn.
Despite being a princess, she rarely acts like one and hates being treated as one. One of the reasons she took a liking towards Ghintec is because when they first met, he neither recognized her as a princess nor treated her as one. Their relationship is so close that she freely allows him to use her real name of Lamhirh when addressing her, something that is very uncommon when addressing those of nobility or royalty.
She acts remarkably older than her age (at her introduction in Crest of the Stars, she is 16 years old) and can, in most cases, logically think her way out of most situations. However, her headstrong nature sometimes clouds her judgement and can lead her to become impulsive. An example of this is when she is reprimanded by Laicch for wishing to stay behind on the Gothlauth instead of continuing her mission of escorting Ghintec to the capital. She believes that she would have been of more use fighting with the crew rather than abandoning them. She is quickly shown how wrong her line of reasoning is and how much more disgraceful it would have been to abandon Ghintec and her mission. She is a remarkably good shot and although she sometimes doubts herself, she proves to be a worthy ship captain (deca-commander) in Banner of the Stars. She shows little emotion throughout Crest of the Stars, but as time goes by became very close friend with Ghintec through Banner of the Stars. This is especially true in later installments, where she more frequently questions how their friendship will last due to the doubt of Ghintec`s lifespan.
She is one of the candidates for the Abh Imperial Throne and, as indicated by her full name, she is the Viscountess of Parhynh, the so-called "Country, or Nation, of Roses."</description>
<picture>14304.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="12" picture="16580.jpg">Kawasumi Ayako</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4081" type="main character in" update="2012-07-25">
<rating votes="168">8.00</rating>
<name>Linn Syun-Rock Dreu Haider Jinto</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Born Jinto Lynn on planet Martine (spelt as Martinh in Baronh) of the Hyde star system (Haïdec in Baronh), he was the son of Rock Lynn, a politician who eventually became president of the Hyde star system. It was during his administration that the Abh empire was able to annex the Hyde stellar system into its territory through an invasion. Making his own ideas more valuable than the rights of the people of Martine, Rock Lin made a deal with the leaders of the invading forces that the territorial lord of Hyde shall be chosen amongst the people of Martine. The leader of the invading forces agreed to this however this meant that an election cannot be held making Rock, as the current leader of Martine, the natural choice to become its territorial lord. Because of this, Rock Lynn, and with him, Jinto, rose to the ranks of Abh nobility as Count of Haïdec.</description>
<picture>20036.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="362" picture="74735.jpg">Imai Yuka</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4082" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="42">8.09</rating>
<name>Abriel Nei Lamsar Larth Balkei Dusanyu</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The current Dusanyu, or Crown Prince, of the Abh Empire of Mankind, the Baronh name of which is Frybar Gloer Gor Bari (Frybarec Gloer Gor Bari), Also the Commander-in-Chief of the Abh Armed Forces, who personally led the invasion of the Hyde star system.</description>
<picture>20035.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1819" picture="20694.jpg">Shiozawa Kaneto</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4083" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="8">9.75</rating>
<name>Trife Boli Yuvdale Remsale</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Despite verging on excessive caution, he is nonetheless one of the most able tacticians in the Labule. He puts every aspect and factor under consideration, frequently asking his subordinates` opinions and assessments before starting an operation. He is also one of the least loved officers.</description>
<picture>20034.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="220" picture="17038.jpg">Kosugi Juurouta</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4084" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="117">8.94</rating>
<name>Spoor Aron Sekpadao Letopanyu Peneju</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>This red-eyed Grand Duchess is one of the most eccentric officers in the Labule, which does not change the fact that she is one of its most able admirals. Though complaining of boredom most of the time, she suddenly springs into action when needed. One of her favourite pastimes is mercilessly teasing Kaselia, her chief of staff.</description>
<picture>20033.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="1509" picture="19311.jpg">Fukami Rika</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4085" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="6">4.06</rating>
<name>Atosryua Syun-Atos Lyuf Raika Febdak Klowal</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The third Baron of Febdak (Faibdash), an obscure star system where Jinto and Lafiel made a stopover en route to Safugnoff (Sfagnaumh). He had an inferiority complex due to his clan`s origins and brief history, causing him to confine and isolate his own father. He tried to abduct Lafiel and imprison Jinto, which brought dire consequences onto himself.</description>
<picture>20032.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4086" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="10">6.47</rating>
<name>Atosryua Syun-Atos Lyuf Raika Febdak Srguf</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>The second Baron of Febdak and father of Klowal. Srguf`s mother was the first Baroness, who gained distinction by rising through the Imperial Star Force, or Labule (Laburec). Due to his being a genetic "grounder," his own son despised him resulting in confinement and isolation. He eventually befriended Jinto and aided Lafiel in "punishing" Klowal. His daughter, Loïc eventually became the Baroness of Febdak and a commanding officer to Lafiel and Jinto.</description>
<picture>20039.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="139" picture="29283.jpg">Koyasu Takehito</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4087" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="1">6.63</rating>
<name>Entoryua Rei</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20044.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="4088" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="2">2.92</rating>
<name>Kaito</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20045.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="3312" picture="24691.jpg">Ikemizu Michihiro</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4089" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="22">7.56</rating>
<name>Ekuryua Wef Tryuz Noel</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20049.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="56" picture="16651.jpg">Shimizu Kaori</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4090" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="3">6.63</rating>
<name>Sobaash Weh Dowl Yuse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20050.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="180" picture="66228.jpg">Saiga Mitsuki</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4091" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="4">6.72</rating>
<name>Samson Bolge Tilsal Tiluse</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20051.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="286" picture="17117.jpg">Ootsuka Akio</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4092" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="7">7.33</rating>
<name>Atosuryua Syun-Atos Baron Febdash Roi</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20052.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="207" picture="25935.jpg">Yamada Miho</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4093" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="6">7.17</rating>
<name>Kufadis Wef Espiel Sespy</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20053.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="375" picture="17221.jpg">Chiba Susumu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4094" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="6">6.88</rating>
<name>Keneeshu Wef Stumal Kipeil</name>
<gender>female</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20054.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="4770" picture="76766.jpg">Suzuka Chiharu</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4095" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="5">2.63</rating>
<name>Bebaus Alon Nerem Nereis</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20055.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="23873.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="4096" type="secondary cast in" update="2009-02-28">
<rating votes="5">2.07</rating>
<name>Bebaus Alon Nerem Nefee</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<picture>20056.jpg</picture>
<seiyuu id="189" picture="23873.jpg">Inoue Kazuhiko</seiyuu>
</character>
<character id="7514" type="appears in" update="2009-05-27">
<rating votes="5">7.65</rating>
<name>Abh Teikoku</name>
<gender>unknown</gender>
<charactertype id="3">Organization</charactertype>
<picture>26171.jpg</picture>
</character>
<character id="40209" type="appears in" update="2012-01-04">
<rating votes="8">4.92</rating>
<name>Diaho</name>
<gender>male</gender>
<charactertype id="1">Character</charactertype>
<description>Jinto`s cat.

Lafiel gave him to Jinto at the end of http://anidb.net/a1 [Seikai no Monshou].
He is the son of Zanelia who is the daughter of Holia.
</description>
<picture>79471.jpg</picture>
</character>
</characters>
<episodes>
<episode id="143" update="2007-05-17">
<epno type="1">1</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-14</airdate>
<rating votes="11">6.24</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">再会</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Reunion</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Saikai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="144" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">2</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-21</airdate>
<rating votes="11">7.34</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">幻炎作戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Operation Phantom Flame</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Gen`en Sakusen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="145" update="2006-03-29">
<epno type="1">3</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-04-28</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">突撃艦"バースロイル"</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Assault Ship Basroil</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Totsugekikan "Basroil"</title>
</episode>
<episode id="146" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">4</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-12</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.82</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">初陣</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The First Campaign</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Uijin</title>
</episode>
<episode id="147" update="2006-01-31">
<epno type="1">5</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-19</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.93</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">華やかな狂気</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Spectacular Insanity</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Hanayaka na Kyouki</title>
</episode>
<episode id="148" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">6</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-05-26</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.90</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">弔いの晩餐</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Remembrance Dinner</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Tomurai no Bansan</title>
</episode>
<episode id="149" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">7</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-02</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.41</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">くらやみの逃亡</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Escape in the Dark</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kurayami no Toubou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="150" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">8</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-09</airdate>
<rating votes="10">5.23</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">決戦前夜</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Eve of the Decisive Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kessen Zenya</title>
</episode>
<episode id="152" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">9</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-16</airdate>
<rating votes="10">6.76</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">バースロイルの戦い</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Basroil`s Battle</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Baasuroiru no Tatakai</title>
</episode>
<episode id="153" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">10</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-23</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.74</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">流れる星</title>
<title xml:lang="en">Shooting Star</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Nagareru Hoshi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="154" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">11</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-06-30</airdate>
<rating votes="10">7.42</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">灼熱の戦場</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Flaming Battlefield</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Shakunetsu no Senjou</title>
</episode>
<episode id="155" update="2006-09-18">
<epno type="1">12</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-07</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.25</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">アプティック門沖会戦</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Battle for Aptic Gate</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Aputikku kato oki kaisen</title>
</episode>
<episode id="156" update="2005-03-10">
<epno type="1">13</epno>
<length>25</length>
<airdate>2000-07-14</airdate>
<rating votes="10">8.62</rating>
<title xml:lang="ja">絆のかたち</title>
<title xml:lang="en">The Shape of Bonds</title>
<title xml:lang="x-jat">Kizuna no Katachi</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39544" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="3">C1</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">4.98</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Opening</title>
</episode>
<episode id="39545" update="2005-08-21">
<epno type="3">C2</epno>
<length>0</length>
<rating votes="2">10.00</rating>
<title xml:lang="en">Ending</title>
</episode>
</episodes>
</anime>
